adperk.com 2011-12-15

# AdPerk Privacy Policy (last modified: January 31, 2011)

AdPerk Privacy Policy (last modified: January 31, 2011)
Highlights
AdPerk recognizes the importance of privacy. The following highlights our Privacy Policy, particularly regarding the
personal information we receive or collect when you use AdPerk. We hope this will help you make an informed
decision about sharing personal information with us.
Use of Information
AdPerk will not sell or share your personally identifiable information (such as name, address or email) with any third-
party without your agreement or consent. Certain personal data are an essential component of AdPerk participation.
For example, your mailing address is necessary to send rewards obtained through the use of the AdPerk platform.
Similarly, your email address is required as part of the AdPerk registration process so we may communicate
important information about your account and the AdPerk program, or so we, or our Reward Sponsors or Co-
sponsors, may provide updates, make special offers or deliver electronic rewards.
Unsubscribing
Unsubscribe or cancel your account whenever you like. Please reference our Terms of Service for more information
on how to unsubscribe or cancel your account.
AdPerk Privacy Policy
This Policy applies to all the services, products or Websites offered or operated by AdPerk.
We're committed to making your AdPerk experience as enjoyable as possible, both on our site and afterwards.
Outlined below are details on the information we collect and how we use it:
1. Information you provide. AdPerk requires personally identifiable information, such as name, email address, mailing
  address and account password) during the registration process. We also collect demographic information at
  various times in the AdPerk experience in order to improve our quality of services and offers to the AdPerk
  community. This information is stored in a secure database to protect user privacy. In some cases, AdPerk may
  report aggregate information to our reward Sponsors or Co-sponsors. Sponsors and Co-sponsors may include
  the sourcing company’s advertisement or Website that resulted in your participation in AdPerk. In addition,
  Sponsors or Co-sponsors may include the companies whose videos you choose to view during your
  participation.
2. AdPerk cookies. When you visit AdPerk, we send one or more cookies (a small file containing a string of
  characters) to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to validate your login session
  and to better understand your interests and preferences so we can provide products, offers and services most
  relevant to you. We will never sell or share personally identifiable information obtained from cookies. Most
  browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate
  when a cookie is being sent. However, some AdPerk features and services may not function properly if cookies
  are disabled.
3. User communications (from you to AdPerk). If you send email or other communication to AdPerk, we may retain
  such communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
4. AdPerk communications (from AdPerk to you). All registrants receive an email confirming their registration and
  participation in AdPerk. Reward notifications and other account or AdPerk-related information might also be sent
  via email. If you choose to opt out of these communications, you will not receive important information about the
  AdPerk program, your account or reward, and may ultimately forfeit your rights to receiving the reward.
5. AdPerk partners. AdPerk offers some rewards in connection with third-parties or other Websites. In registering
  with AdPerk, you agree that Sponsors, Co-sponsors or companies whose goods or services you obtain or
  attempt to obtain through AdPerk, may contact you by email or ground mail (for example, you may receive
  communications from vendors from which you’ve earned a reward, or updates from retailers providing gift cards);
  however, we will not sell or divulge your personal information to Advertisers or other third-parties without your
  consent.
6. Links and other sites. AdPerk may present links to our Sponsors and Co-sponsors in a format that enables us to
  keep track whether these links are followed. Once you leave the AdPerk Website you are subject to the privacy
                                                          Page 1

   policy of the hosting site and we do not exercise control over any site or links accessed from our network of
   services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit
   personal information from you.
7. "Tell-A-Friend" Information: If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about AdPerk, we will ask you
   for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or
   her to visit the Sites, and we do not store this information.
8. IP addresses. We record IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to prevent abuse of our
   service. Your particular IP address and related information is never sold or shared with third-parties of any kind.
Special Note to International Users
The AdPerk Websites are hosted in the United States and intended for and directed to users in the U.S. If you are a
consumer accessing the Websites from Canada, the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or
regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from U.S. laws, please be advised that
through your continued use of the Websites, which are governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy, you are
transferring your personal information to the U.S. and you consent to that transfer.
Acceptance of this Privacy Policy
By using the AdPerk Website you are agreeing to the terms herein, as well as the AdPerk Terms of Service. If you do
not agree to the Policy as described herein, please do not use the AdPerk Website. We reserve the right, at our
discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time. Please check this page frequently
for changes. Your continued use of AdPerk signals your acceptance of the Policy as it exists at all times you use the
AdPerk Website.
If you have any questions about this Policy, please email us at: privacy@adperk.com.
